polijam.com 2009-12-15

# PoliJAM Privacy Policy

  |  Privacy Policy |    
---|---|---  
  |   |    
  | We at PoliJAM are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat personal information received about you when you visit PoliJAM.com. |    
  |   |    
  | **What information do we collect?** |    
  | We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data: |    
  | 

  * information about your computer and about your visits to and use of the PoliJAM website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views which will allow us to evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our website; 
  * information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with PoliJAM;
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters;
  * information that you provide to us via email to PoliJAM or a PoliJAM employee;
  * and any other information that you choose to send to us.

|    
  |   |    
  | **Cookies** |    
  | We use cookies on this website to allow us to estimate our total audience size and traffic to help us improve our website so that we can provide you with the news and stories that you want to see.  A cookie is a text file that is sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. |    
  | We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the web site's usability and for marketing purposes.  We may also use that information to recognize your computer when you visit our website, and to personalize our website for you.  Our third party network advertisers may also send you cookies.  To learn more about the choices you have about the cookies our third party network advertisers may send you please refer to their privacy policies. |    
  | We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of your personally identifiable information.  Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.  (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.)  This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites (including this one). |    
  |   |    
  | **Using your personal data** |    
  | Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. |    
  | We may use your personal information to: |    
  | 

  * administer the website;
  * improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
  * enable your use of the services available on the website;
  * send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
  * send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
  * send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
  * send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
  * send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications (relating to our business [or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by emailing us at  [ info@polijam.com](mailto:info@polijam.com));
  * provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user; 
  * deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and
  * we will not provide your personal information to any third parties.

|    
  |   |    
  | **Other disclosures** |    
  | In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you: |    
  | 

  * when in good faith, we believe that we are required to do so by law;
  * in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  * in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
  * if we believe it is necessary or appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets in the website. 

|    
  |   |    
  | **Security of your personal data** |    
  | We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to safeguard and prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  Of course, data transmission over the Internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet. |    
  |   |    
  | **Policy amendments** |    
  | PoliJAM reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.   |    
  |   |    
  | **Third party websites** |    
  | The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. |    
  |   |    
  | **Updating information** |    
  | Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. |    
  |   |    
  | **Contact** |    
  | If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email at  [ info@polijam.com](mailto:info@polijam.com).  |    
  |   |
